[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Lily] I know you bombed my properties!
And you sabotaged my shipment.
An eye for an eye, Red Dragon.
[Lily] You know what you deserve?
What you deserve is a slow death
that eats at your soul.
You deserve to feel every ounce of pain!
-You'll suffer so bad
-[screams]
and so much that you'll long
for death instead!
Sir. We're just waiting for Diego.
[Pandoy] Loring! Run, Loring!
[gunshot]
[Loring] Pandoy!
Don't! No!
[gunshot]
You bastard!
[doctor] I'm so sorry.
We did everything we could,
but they'd both lost too much blood.
They'll pay for this.
They'll pay for this!
[Arnaldo] I haven't met you,
but I can't stop myself
from thinking about you.
I always see you in my dreams.
Why does it feel like
I'm in love with you?
Until the last drop of her blood spills,
I'll plan her demise.
I just need for you to execute
the perfect crime.
I want you to kill Lily Cruz.
I'm scared! If you could
only see yourself right now.
[Lily] It's like you're ready to kill!
I won't let you turn into
a criminal, Diego!
[Diego] But there's no place
for justice here in Ardiente!
I will kill them.
-Diego, don't! Diego!
-[Jepoy] Diego!
[door slams]
[dramatic music playing]
[panting]
[shouting in agony]
[shouting] No! No!
[dramatic music playing]
[shouting] No!
[ominous music playing]
[Diego] I swear to you
that I'll make them all pay
for what they did to you.
All the abuse…
All the lies and treachery…
and all the evil I ignored
because I believed in hope and change…
[slow tense music playing]
The old Diego Torillo is gone.
All that's left
is a man thirsty
for the blood of his enemies!
[somber music playing]
Come on, Lily.
No, Mom.
We should leave Diego alone for now.
[somber music playing]
If they're already buried,
then just let their corpses rot already.
You know the problem with those lowlifes?
They're too emotional.
Just a bunch of softies!
So, Governor, have I redeemed myself?
[Julio chuckles]
[sinister music playing]
Talk to me again
when I'm seated
behind my desk in the capitol.
Speaking of… I want to see Judge Lustre.
I want to make sure
that nothing will prevent
the dismissal
of Camia Cruz's case against me.
Yes, Governor.
Emilia, would you please stop chitchatting
with whoever that is?
Come here and help me celebrate
because I just one-upped Lily Cruz's camp.
Hmm…
I don't know if I should
tell you this, Papa,
because we're not allies anymore.
And Mama is not doing so good
because Lily Cruz has found out
that she's Red Dragon.
You…
Well, whatever!
Look at how things are turning out.
Meanwhile, I'll be returning
to my position!
Do you really think you can
get back your position?
No, no, no.
Because Diego Torillo will make sure
that you go to prison.
Hey! Listen!
Go to the garden.
You know those flowers
that scatter on the grass?
The ones called wildflowers?
You see, even if no one tends to them,
they can survive on their own.
They reproduce.
But there are some plants
that even when stepped on or crushed
or even poisoned,
won't just die.
They even cause harm to other plants.
You know what they're called?
They're called weeds.
Now, you and I… we're like that.
We're like weeds that
are difficult to get rid of.
So, you see,
there is such a thing as forever
or everlasting.
You're a funeral wreath.
How did I deserve such a daughter?
[exhales sharply]
[crickets chirping]
Jepoy.
[soft music playing]
Diego's bottled up so much pain and rage
caused by the Ardientes' crimes
against him.
His anger will consume him, Lily.
Just like how our anger
towards Arnaldo changed us
after he killed Nanny Carlotta.
I will never forget
how Diego tried to stop me
then when I couldn't control my anger.
We only use guns, to protect ourselves.
I can't believe you!
[Anna] Jepoy!
You think you're an angel
but this town isn't a
place for angels, Diego!
Fine, go and kill. Let's all kill!
How will that make us
any different from them?!
He really tried to stop me,
to the point that we almost fought.
As much as I want to support him,
I'm honestly worried for him now, Lily.
Because he's changed.
[sighs]
No. Diego can't… Diego won't kill anyone.
We shouldn't be scared.
Diego wouldn't do such a thing.
He will come to his senses.
He'll realize that violence
isn't necessary to seek revenge.
We don't have to kill people…
to find justice.
[soft music continues playing]
Diego will realize that.
I believe in him.
I know Diego.
I know he'll do what's right.
[foreboding music playing]
[tense music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[Arnaldo] I need to see you again, Lily.
[soft piano music playing]
[Lily] No. Diego can't…
Diego won't kill anyone. I believe in him.
I know Diego.
I know he'll do what's right.
[Diego] There's no place
for justice in Ardiente!
So, let's stop fooling ourselves.
I will kill them.
Diego, don't. Please, listen to me.
I will kill them!
-Diego!
-[Jepoy] Diego!
[somber music playing]
[Loring] What's all that?
[Lily] Since it's Mr. Pandoy's birthday…
Hold on. Wait.
-[Pandoy] Are all those for me?
-[Lily] Yes. And these too.
-Wow!
-This one's from my mom.
This is a lot.
-These are from Anna and Jepoy.
-I'm very grateful. Thank you.
[Loring] Wow! Look at this!
[somber music continues playing]
I'll get you some take-out later.
It'll be our secret.
Thanks, Nanny.
[Diego] Grandpa, it hurts!
[Julio] Feel the pain!
[Loring] It's okay.
I'll make it all better, Diego.
-It hurts!
-I'm here.
[young Diego crying]
[Loring] Wait, who was the girl
you gave the flowers to?
-[Pandoy] You're just jealous.
-Jealous?
-Someone's jealous.
-No, I'm not!
No one's as handsome as my dearest Diego.
Hey, hey, hey. What about me?
[Loring] You? Wow.
[Diego] Now who's jealous?
[dramatic music playing]
If you still respect me
as your second father,
you won't pick a fight with the Ardientes!
I won't let them kill you too!
I'm sorry if… if I made you worry.
Forget that, Diego.
What's important is you're home.
[sobbing]
[phone ringing]
[cancels call]
[voice prompt] The
subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
[tense music playing]
Lily.
Mom, I need to go to Diego.
[ominous music playing]
Diego…
I know you want to be alone right now.
But I'm sorry, I can't give you that.
I don't want to leave you.
That's why I'm here.
What are you going to do with that gun?
Diego, we already talked about this.
We aren't murderers.
This isn't the way.
This isn't right, Diego.
[tense music playing]
Diego, I want to protect you…
because I understand the pain
you're going through right now.
And until now, I still feel the same pain.
But I will never let that…
turn me into a murderer.
I'm here to protect you.
I'm here to save you.
Diego, please listen to me.
Diego, please listen.
Don't let your hatred cloud
your principles.
Diego, please.
Killing other people…
won't give you the justice you want.
[somber music playing]
Diego, please.
[Diego] I'm not the same
Diego Torillo you knew.
And I'll never be that man again.
Now, I've realized
that the world is a cruel place,
and principles have no place in it.
That's why I will kill Sanggano.
[Lily] Diego, wait.
[Diego] And if you're going to stop me,
then we best go our separate ways.
Forgive me.
[tense music playing]
Lily, I'm afraid of what Diego might do.
He's consumed by anger, Mom.
His eyes were full of rage.
I felt that way too
when they killed Dad.
When I thought I lost you,
[soft music playing]
and when they killed Nanny Carlotta.
That was exactly how I felt.
That's why, deep inside,
I can feel every ounce of anger and pain…
that now resides in Diego's heart.
I feel his rage blinding him.
His desire to seek revenge,
and his thirst for justice…
All those emotions… were
exactly what I felt once before.
[sighs]
But what if Diego
pushes through with his plan?
No, Mom. I don't want to think about it.
[crying]
[Ivy sighs]
The man I saw earlier
wasn't the Diego I knew.
He was fuming.
And it scares me, Mom.
But even though…
Though he's pushing me away,
I'll continue to be there for him.
[somber music playing]
Those pests who were
protecting Diego are now dead.
And Lily Cruz now knows that
Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
So, how can this day get even better?
[lawyer] Well, all the witnesses
from Camia Cruz's camp
have backed out.
And you know what that means.
The court will find her case
weak without a witness.
They'll have a hard time
calling a hearing.
I'm not the presiding judge,
but I have a lot of connections, Julio.
[chuckling]
And before we know it,
the case will be dissolved.
Victory won't be Julio Ardiente's.
Yes, we have a lot on our plate,
but if he thinks
I'll stop going after him,
well, he's dead wrong.
[lawyer] What if they find new witnesses?
Will you still honor them, Judge?
I know Camia and Attorney
Fisher. They won't give up.
I'm going to set a meeting
with Judge Lustre.
The judge getting into bed
with Julio Ardiente.
And if I need to bargain with him
just to prevent Julio
from assuming power, I'll do it.
Wait, attorney.
We're in the right.
We don't need to play their game.
Attorney, come on.
Diego's foster parents are dead.
Lily Cruz is busy
chasing after Red Dragon.
You know, they're like bees
whose hive just fell off a tree.
They're rattled.
While all of this is happening,
I will slowly sneak into the capitol
and claim the position
that is rightfully mine.
[tense music playing]
Governor of Ardiente.
The king is back!
-I'll drink to that.
-Cheers!
Cheers, Governor!
[men laughing]
This truly is a lovely day.
We have to secure an advantage
before Julio's camp does.
And the evidence against Red Dragon?
All evidences are admissible in court.
We need a…
A credible witness.
[suspenseful music playing]
I know someone.
And I know where to find her.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
[Lily] You should be here, Diego,
looking for justice that we both want.
[doorbell rings]
Lily?
We need to talk.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Mercedes] There has been a lot
of security breach lately.
We need to tighten security
from the inside out.
Am I clear on that?
-Yes, ma'am.
You may go.
Mercedes, this came in for you.
[slow tense music playing]
From Red Dragon?
You may go.
[door closes]
[Mercedes] Let your plans be
dark and impenetrable as night.
And when you move,
fall like a thunderbolt.
Burn this after reading.
Follow the instructions until the end.
Destroy all the important files
proving that Helena Montoya is Red Dragon.
Do this in the dead of night.
Nobody should find out.
Be unpredictable as lightning.
[ominous music playing]
I need you to give a statement
against Red Dragon.
But, Lily…
This can only go two ways, Myla.
Either we fight
and you end up losing again,
or you tell me everything you know.
Nothing more, nothing less.
[tense music playing]
[Myla] Telling on Mercedes
is one thing, Lily.
But telling on Red Dragon is another.
I know she'll get back at me if I do that.
Don't you know what she's capable of?
She can take everything away from us.
If I don't get to her first. I assure you,
nothing bad will happen to you
as long as you're with me.
That said, tell me everything you know
that could serve as evidence
against Red Dragon.
[tense music playing]
Take this blue book to Romulo.
I told him to keep this safe.
We'll need this for
Red Dragon's transactions.
Tell Romulo to keep it away
from anyone we don't trust.
Understood?
All right.
I'll stand as your witness against her.
But I don't have any documents or evidence
against Red Dragon.
Only Mercedes and Romulo have those.
You better hurry, Lily.
Now that Red Dragon knows
you know her identity,
she could already be destroying
any possible evidence
that might reveal her secrets.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Thanks, boss.
-Cheers.
[Jose] I'm telling you.
There's no way Julio Ardiente
will have me killed.
[chuckles]
Never! If it weren't for me,
that old man would've
been found in a rubbish dump.
I'm the only man he trusts now.
He can't even rely
on his grandson anymore.
Boss, you should've killed Diego Torillo.
Julio wouldn't have slammed you,
and just given you a bonus--
Shut up!
It wasn't easy taking him down,
unlike those old geezers. But that's fine.
Because now, the idiot's crying a river.
[tense music playing]
But that Torillo better be careful.
One wrong move and he'll meet
his aunt and uncle in purgatory.
Mark my words!
[goon] Cheers to that, boss.
[tense music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Let's finish this up.
Hi.
Madam Emilia, you can't go any further.
What the hell?
Mercedes strictly prohibited anyone
from entering the chamber.
She'll see you when she's done.
First, it's Mama. Now, it's Mercedes.
What can she be busy
with that she can't see me?
She's busy carrying out
Madam Red Dragon's orders.
[sarcastic] Okay. No problem.
-[henchwoman] I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Okay.
Wait! Wait! Sorry.
Sorry.
Yes, Emilia?
Looking for something?
Didn't Mama give you orders?
Also, are you trying to keep us apart?
You know, I'm sure my mama
would want you to fill me in
on her plans too
because I am her daughter.
I don't remember her
mentioning you at all, really.
I guess I'm the one she trusts
to handle her businesses.
But don't worry, Emilia.
Your mother loves you.
I'm sure she will reach out to you soon.
I know.
She loves me because I am her daughter,
and you're not.
Besides, she already called me.
Good. That way,
you won't need to meddle
in the instructions she gave me.
Goodbye, Emilia.
[Emilia] Excuse me.
[tense music playing]
[goon] He's drunk.
Boss, I can't drink anymore.
I'm going now.
-You're such a weakling.
-Don't mind him. Let him go.
-Go home to your wife.
-[Jose] Cheers, cheers.
-Sir.
-Let's drink some more, Boss.
[suspenseful music playing]
[gunshots]
[gunshot]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[gunshots]
[tense music playing]
New package for you.
-[screams]
-Sorry, ma'am.
You idiot! Watch where you walk!
Sorry, ma'am.
We're very sorry, ma'am.
Please let us clean it for you.
Here's your jacket, ma'am.
Thank you.
Good day, Madam Mercedes.
[tense music playing]
Madam Mercedes.
It has a nice ring to it.
[tense music playing]
He will win, who prepares himself.
Wait to take the enemy unprepared.
[Mercedes] Once you've gathered
all the documents,
you must store them in the vault.
Then, wait for my next instructions.
[tense music playing]
Come on, Mercedes.
Can't you read it a bit louder?
[tense music playing]
Sahara.
Yes, Madam Mercedes?
Prepare the vault.
Yes, Madam.
[ominous music playing]
Aren't you supposed
to help your mother out?
Yeah, but I'm so annoyed by
her daughter-wannabe.
She's so irritating.
And they don't realize
that they'll need me someday.
Especially since so many people
are targeting Mama's business.
Why would she be a target?
What's her business, anyway?
It's all legal, right?
Of course, it is.
And you know, Mama, right?
Can we just not talk about her?
I'm going to sleep
and have my beauty rest.
Good night, my dear husband.
[Raul] I'll uncover your
mother's secrets eventually.
I just hope it's not what I think.
But for now, my son needs me.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to see my son.
Wait, which one?
Because I can only think of one
you always like to call
but never answers the phone.
Stop it, Emilia. Diego's in mourning.
So why don't you just send him
flowers or a card
and call it a day?
What a grouch. At least I can sleep now.
[pensive music playing]
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[Raul] Son, you need to pick up. Diego.
[phone continues ringing]
Diego, pick up.
Diego? Diego, where are you?
I want to see you.
Diego?
[tense music playing]
[Lily] In every letter and every
detail, I study my enemy.
In turn, their strength
becomes mine as well.
Such is the art of war.
[bottles clanking]
Son.
What's wrong?
Why do you keep refusing my help?
Especially now that you know
about the secret I keep.
I'm looking for Sanggano.
Why? What do you want with Sanggano?
I'm going to kill him.
[tense music playing]
[Raul sighs]
You know what, Diego?
Those kinds of things…
You don't have to do that.
Just let me take care of it. I'll do it.
Because I won't… I don't want
anything bad happening to you.
[Diego] No!
I'll be the one to end Sanggano.
Me!
[tense music playing]
Here, Boss.
[goon 1] Let's drink, Boss.
[goon 2] Boss, let's drink.
[tense music playing]
[goon 1] Looks like
your wound still hurts.
Boss, I'm off to the men's room.
Do whatever you want.
Hi, baby.
[goon 1] Boss, I'm impressed.
You're still in the mood
to go drinking even after
what happened with Diego.
He's an amateur.
He couldn't even shoot me right.
[Jose] I'd like to see him
try to shoot me again.
Baby, that hurts.
-It does?
-Can you kiss the pain away?
-I think it got better, baby.
-Does it still hurt?
Here. It hurts here, baby.
-Where does it hurt?
-Baby, it hurts.
Can you kiss the pain away?
Can you kiss me again?
Ouch. This one hurts too.
[goon 1] Boss.
Boss, I'll go have a little fun.
[Jose] Hello, baby! Hi!
Does it still hurt?
Yes. Can you kiss me here too?
It still hurts. Here.
[indistinct chatter]
[grunts]
-Here?
-[Jose] Ouch.
[tense music playing]
Can you?
Then go ahead.
You don't have the guts!
Shoot me!
[Jose and Diego grunting]
[tense music playing]
[gunshot]
[laughing hysterically]
[continues laughing]
Amateur.
[taunting]
[laughing]
[coughing]
[Jose retching]
[tense music swells]
Red Dragon wants to recruit
Diego Torillo to the group.
[Jepoy] Are you nuts?
Julio Ardiente will have you killed
for killing Sanggano!
-You know that, right?
-I'm not afraid to die.
[Julio] Lily Cruz lied to you,
and so did Diego.
Those two ganged up on you.
While we're corrupting Diego Torillo,
it'll only make it worse for Lily Cruz.
I won't join your group as an underling.
I want to join as Red Dragon's ally.
Red Dragon is Helena Montoya.
But there's something missing.
[Lily] I'll find it.
[in Chinese] Hello, Mercedes.
[theme music playing]